Every great athlete, after a big game,
does one thing without fail.
They review the game tape.
They don't just do it to beat themselves up
over their mistakes, they do it to learn.
They watch with their eyes like a coach,
objective and curious.
Your life experiences are your game tape.
The highs, the lows, the turning points,
they all contain powerful data about your passions,
what truly matters to you,
and especially your resilience.
But let's be clear about what resilience means here.
It isn't about how fast you bounce back,
it's about how fully you learn while you're down,
ensuring every comeback is smarter, not just stronger.
In the final drill for this lesson,
we're going to prompt you to review your tape
with that lens.
First, I want you to think about a specific moment
in your career when you felt truly alive and successful,
a peak performance moment.
What was that project?
What was that specific role?
Now, success isn't always a straight line.
Sometimes the most powerful parts of your success formula
are forged in moments that start with a no.
I remember pitching my big idea to executives
at two NFL franchises and getting denied.
I was disappointed, frustrated,
I felt inadequate and a little embarrassed,
but the mental muscle of resilience kicked in
and forged a new belief for me.
I would say this,
I stand on a mountain of nos to get to one yes.
Three years later, I got that yes.
And a once rejected idea became the first ever
player brand university in professional sports.
As you think about your peak performance,
don't just look at the final win,
look at the resilience it took to get there.
That is your success formula.
Then I want you to think about a time
when you faced a significant challenge or setback.
We look back, not with judgment, but with curiosity.
These key plays from your life
contain the final set of clues we need
to build your powerful M.V.P. blueprint.
Resilience reveals what truly matters,
what sustains you and it tests what you've outgrown.
Learning from your past gives you the tools
to lead through what's next.